<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE report PUBLIC "-//Norman Walsh//DTD DocBk XML V1.4//EN" "http://docbook.org/docbook/xml/1.4/db3xml.dtd">
<report>
  <repheader>
    <title>Report of my work on project SCXML2SVG(pb138)</title>
    <author>
      <firstname>Dobroslav</firstname>
      <surname>Bernáth</surname>
    </author>
    <abstract>
      <title>Project SCXML to SVG Web Application</title>
    </abstract>
  </repheader>

  <section>
    <title>Team Creation</title>
    <para>
      Together with Adam Brenkuš we were looking for suitable project from themes. SCXML2SVG seemed like interesting theme and with team members such as Jozef Hornych
      and Ivan Hrádek we were happy about the future of project. As I have some experiences in team leading and project management I decided to take this role.
    </para>
    <title>Project Beginning</title>
    <para>
      At the start of project analysis we had little argument about which way of implementing problem we take. In the end we decided to make our project more robust
      and reusable in future. I've chosen roles and work for others and begin to work on main web application funkctions.
    </para>
    <title>Project(Story) Continues</title>
    <para>
      Main functionality such as download and upload was completed rather quickly. After that I came with an idea to implement try button to make it easier for user
      to work with his SCXML file on our web. This new idea together with show svg button surprisingly show itslef as a problem. Fortunately I managed to solve it.
    </para>
    <para>
      <title>End of Implementation and Fixing(We will just put it together and it will work right?)</title>
      This part of project was probably most problematic due to hard compatibility of using different versions of Tomcat among team members, relative and absolute paths
      to certain documents and files, which is problem of programming web application I think. Thankfully we had high quality implementation from Adam and Jozef with 
      minimum bugs, so we managed to finalize the project.
    </para>
    <para>
      <title>The end</title>
      In the end I can honestly say that Iam quite happy about the result of our project. I would also like to thank my team mates for their great will to finish project and
      their work on project, without which it wouldnt be possible.
    </para>
  </section>
</report>

